

Francisco Gouveia

Date of birth: 15/12/1998

Nationality: Portuguese

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Rua 1 de Julho Edifício Brava Golden R\C Q, 9350-206 Ribeira Brava, Portugal



(+351) 966620246

https://github.com/Franch1co

LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/francisco-

gouveia-879536235/



ABOUT ME

I'm Francisco, I'm 23 years old and I'm in the last year of the Degree in Computer Engineering at the University of Madeira. Throughout my degree I was able to learn several programming languages, which allowed me to understand how different technologies and programming languages connect with each other. I consider myself a professional with good communication skills, persistent, motivated, who I oves new challenges and loves to learn new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

03/2022 - CURRENT - Funchal, Madeira, Portugal

Software developer

Nearsoft Solutions - Curricular Internship

Development of specific web channels for user registration with interfaces for some types of business.

01/07/2021 - 30/07/2021 - Funchal, Madeira, Portugal

Summer Internship

David Aveiro - ITI (Interactive Tecnologies Institute)

In this internship I worked on the development of programming features in components of the Dynamic Information System Modeller and Executer (DISME) platform using technologies like Laravel (PHP) and Angular (TypeScript), under supervision of David Aveiro (PhD), promoted by the ITI/ ARDITI/UMa business engineering laboratory.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2018 - CURRENT - Campus Universitário da Penteada, Funchal - Portugal

Degree in Informatics Engineering

Universidade da Madeira

https://www.uma.pt/en/ensino/1o-ciclo/licenciatura-em-engenharia-informatica/

12/2021 - 02/2022

The Web Developer BootCamp 2022

Udemy, online courses

Online course of 63 hours about web development, it covers many tools about how to build a website using technologies like HTML, CSS, JS, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB and much more.

https://www.udemy.com/course/the-web-developer-bootcamp/

09/2017 – 07/2018 – Campus Universitário da Penteada, Funchal - Portugal, Portugal

Degree in Economics - 1st year

Universidade da Madeira

https://www.uma.pt/en/ensino/1o-ciclo/licenciatura-em-economia/

2013 – 2017 – Rua Padre Leão Henriques nº 14, Ponta do Sol - Madeira, Portugal

Sciences and Technologies

Escola Básica e Secundaria da Ponta do Sol

https://escolas.madeira-edu.pt/ebspsol/Início/tabid/1750/Default.aspx

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Portuguese

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Writing Listening Reading Spoken Spoken В1 В1 production interaction В1 В1 В1

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B1 **Driving Licence:** B

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Free time activities and personal interests:

- Gym and exercise
- Motorsport fan Reading books
- Like to see documentaries about various topics
- Enthusiastic about technology and video game industry